morning's copies we zip up my maverick
joggers here maverick joggers brah most
lit merch in the game after our martiai
it's not even true Logan Falls where
it's just way letter um
so I'm in downtown West Portal take you
guys there let's go for a little walk
and I'm not walking right now I'm not in
the car um I went out to breakfast man a
coffee shop right over there go to the
really depressing bar yo yo I'm not
going to the depressing bar I don't even
know what the depressing bar is like
midday on a Sunday bro but what I'm here
to show you guys is some retail space
right next to edible arrangements this
retail or lease it was a travel agent
and we know travel agents aren't really
doing too well so can you guys hear me
well I got the air funds the retail
space right see is it open
locked um but what do you guys think of
a comma a I store
oh yeah sounds good bro got that got
that air pods yo what do you guys think
of a comma a I store we'll get a store
it's gonna sell yawns it's gonna sell
pandas it's gonna sell Commerce maze
it's gonna sell debug boards it's gonna
sell everything yeah pop up my shop man
we're gonna get no the merch has got to
get we got to really step up our merch
game I don't want to be like a tech
company I want to have the best merch
and I think we can do it have we
considered a kiosk you mean those things
at the middle of the mall no respect
they get no respect right like the
t-mobile store but it's not the store
it's like the little kiosk with the two
people and they don't have anywhere to
go
considering the niche audience but I
mean you know hey yo look look you guys
let me tell you about why I do khamenei
I am I trying to be profitable I mean
yes am I trying to build a successful
business yes but we really do it because
it's fun if it wasn't fun why would we
do it and and that's what I'm saying
right doesn't it sound fun
we'll open up the comma a I retail store
um we've also recently come into some
money so we have money and that's the
real reason that's gonna be the topic of
Skokie Sunday we're hiring the product
team I'm talking about Schiffer I'm
talking about open pilot we need people
we need infrastructure people and people
who know react JavaScript developers um
there's a comma army if you guys know
anybody I probably look weird walking
like dad this isn't LA you know I don't
know if you can just do this like walk
around West Portal with periscope get
that selfie angle right
let's go
let's go more to the backroads here by
the way I just want to take a minute to
thank the omnipresent modern cell phone
network that makes this all possible
it's just it's just amazing I got an old
comma hoody on this is this is old hoody
stuff but yeah so we are hiring if you
guys if you guys know anything no no no
no no don't think of it as a retail
store think of it as the comma
experience store I'm not in London I'm
in West Portal so that's kind of where
our shops gonna be yeah but do you
consider react phonons from outside the
US only if you can work in the US so we
don't do we don't do any remote work I'm
all work is in our San Francisco office
it keeps the team all on the same page
but yeah if you're outside the US it
depends on what country you're in if
you're in a country with an e3 visa
that's easy h-1b is a little harder if
you qualify for no one look at make that
happen
we're hiring for people what do I think
about the immigration in Sweden I have
no opinion I'm not in Sweden bro
I know PewDiePie moved to London that's
all I know about Sweden I didn't move to
London what do you move Brighton yeah
and that's not the same Brighton that
mmm talks about on underground the only
good song on on relapse yeah yo what up
so so yeah that's really what I'm here
to talk to you guys about today we are
hiring react infrastructure guys the bar
also is insanely high our interviews are
just they're brutal but but but here's
the difference between startups and
comma AI they say their change in the
world we are actually out here doing it
that's right comma army well I partner
with Logan Paul we don't partner with
nobody man but hey if Logan Paul wants
to shout me out I wouldn't I wouldn't
object but yeah last big hill I'm
walking up guys big hill what's the
salary like ah
120 maybe 140 um do we pay with exposure
yeah I'm burning calories right what's
what's exposed it's about fun it really
is about fun we just want to make the
best products um that's why it's really
about you know I was reading sometimes I
read some time I read yeah we do equity
I mean it's a trade-off right if you
want to get 140 K you're not gonna get
too many shares if you want to take a
lower salary you get more and more
equity right it's just a trade-off did I
bring water
hey Eddie's here you can't buy fun
that's right you can't find fun but you
having a lot of money helps we're gonna
move to LA we're gonna rent a mansion
we're gonna call ourselves team eleven
yeah team eleven yeah yeah he's a
trade-off equity versus salary but yeah
so we are we are we have recently come
into some money which is great we love
money and not just from selling our
products though it's profitable you guys
and you guys you guys are making that
happen yeah what 40k in San Francisco is
pretty good you'll be you'll be doing
fine that's more than anyone's getting
paid right now but like I said we
recently uh we recently came into some
some money so you know money is is
always good how big is the team uh I
don't know somewhere between like 10 and
13 I got a count yes so so we look
honestly here's what I look for in the
interviews can you think can you think
that's it that's it like I love
questions like how much would you charge
to wash all the windows in Seattle right
that's a great question not a
brainteaser question brainteaser
questions are stupid because that's do
you see the trick but like you know
you're asking about washing windows and
in Seattle it's about how people break
that question down and think because
that's super relevant to to everything
you want to do do I have a car with
doors that open like this you know what
guys I started out I learned about
business from three places
I watched the Silicon Valley TV show I
read Donald Trump's the art of the deal
the best business book of all time I
heard
and I watched Eric Cartman but I've
learned that none of those were really
good sources of business information so
no we don't have doors that go like this
I Drive around in a Prius with antennas
on the roof and an apple in Ex that
actually costs more than the fries
anything that has helped me in thinking
a problem-solving bro just thinking
everyone's gotta think thinking it's out
these days but we're trying to bring
thinking back we're trying to bring
thinking back that's what we do in the
collar army you guys read books always
think always ask why you can do it
do I know what ROI means return on
investment bro if you got in the comma
seed round your return on investment
whoo
radio on the Internet you want to bring
open pile to indoor moving platforms not
only talk cars different routes people
take to solve problems yeah I mean
really the question is like are you
gonna think or are you reciting
something you've heard before because
you're reciting something you've heard
before how are you ever gonna make
anything new we are making new shit at
khamenei I listen guys I know look okay
I know a self-driving car end of the
year under $1,000 that sounded cool
right um everything you've seen from us
you know like pandas and eons it's stuff
that exists we have three announcements
lined up for you this year and all three
of them are things the world has never
seen before all three of them are things
that are really gonna push push the
future forward because you've got to
build a solid infrastructure before you
can push the future forward and I think
that's what we've been doing with the
Aeons and pandas is that a Nissan Leaf
as a Nissan Leaf the Nissan Leaf honked
at me I guess it got angry that I called
it a Nissan Leaf Oh bro bro why you
angry bro no BS you started the
singularity hasn't happened yet our
money from investment um bro you think
I'm selling IP no we got money don't
worry about that we got money yeah the
singularity has started I agree ha the
world's getting crazy the world is
getting crazy every day it just gets
gets a little bit crazier it's hard to
keep up with everything
but um you know you got to filter out
the fake news you got to filter out the
crab you got to stay on top of what's
real what do I think of way mo uber oh
god I don't know man I just hate the
company sue each other
it just doesn't move the world forward
who knows who actually did what it
sounds like somebody like paid some
somebody did something sketchy somebody
paid somebody whatever do you that's the
thing you don't even want to play that
game right you just gotta be you know
it's like when the regulators came to me
right you don't want to play that game
you don't want to buy into their frame
you got to make your own frame you guys
got to be a maverick and dent the
universe out I can write I can't just
deal Logan Paulson catchphrases um okay
how does comma AI compared with way mo
and Tesla so you can google that but
everything public lightweight maps are
the way to go no we have a different
strategy the problem with the
lightweight maps is you're really
constraining the axes on which you can
localize they're doing lanes and science
yeah I don't know what if you don't have
lanes or what if you don't have signs
those are very like feature dependent
our Maps are much more generic than that
we using features but not lanes and
science using that computers in the
traditional TV sense what up guys I'm on
a bench thoughts on crypto currencies
hot Oh bro huddle I huh
doing good I wish coming I bought some
but she wasn't Eve man if we bought some
eath right when kama started uh we'd be
doing great what's my IQ I don't know
why um people who like talk about like
the number it's like Oh 160 IQ and I
call it on YouTube and talk shit on your
video okay bro um you're buying a black
e Oh Oh guys that's the other thing I
want to talk to you about um well never
using litem I see other thing I want to
talk to you about when will things ship
starting the 15th and you know when I
say something on Twitter I'm no Elon
Musk I come through on the date on the
15th we are going to be shipping
everything out from our store within
three days of you ordering it not not to
brag on Elon Musk but his Twitter
predictions like if he was putting his
money where his mouth is on Twitter
predictions you'd be good betting
against them big fan but you know you
got to be real I'm being real is
important but our experience guys you
know we just want we just want oh man I
love winning I run I want to win so bad
I love winning
oh man winnings great George Hotz is Ida
about Ida there's anyone at the house
love this man let's go go through the
comedy backyard we'll go comment I
backyard where are we now greats go for
good Skokie yo where are we right now we
are outside the comment not the team 11
management that's we're gonna get that
in L I know but seriously guys what do
you think retail spot we're gonna start
shipping everything out mad fast we're
even thinking about putting some of our
products on Amazon but don't bet on that
buy I'm shop that calm down yeah I go
you know comments on a I shopped at
comedy I go right now gray pandas - yeah
you guys what are a ton of gray pandas I
mean it might be hard to meet the
deadline but uh no we've done actually a
lot a lot of people have ordered a lot
of a lot of gray pin is can you invest
in comma AI know private equity only uh
other than working on Toyota what's the
main thing we want to accomplish guys
this year is gonna be crazy
this year I'm telling you we got three
things lined up and I can't tell you
about any of them yet but you're just
gonna see one thing after another you're
gonna be like that's crazy and then
you'd be another thing you'd be like
that's crazy and those give me another
could be like that's crazy
alright cuz they're new they're new
they're the kind of things that the
world has never seen before and and
that's what we're doing here come a I um
oh yeah oh yeah this year that this year
did I cut my hair myself no no no no no
we have oh we have in office haircuts um
I don't really care what I look like I
don't really care what people think of
me I care about what I'm doing I care
about I care about making things better
it doesn't matter what my hair looks
like oh you know I get
[Laughter]
SAE level for lidar why do you need
lidar are humans level for a Corolla
support has shipped if you have a
Corolla you can install them pile zero
point four point two right now on your
Corolla and it'll work thank you fam
form them um yeah Coelho support has
shipped presenta bility and impressions
matter bro if I thought that stuff
mattered when I get on TechCrunch and
scream like I'm hyperventilating talk
really fast no because that's the point
that that stuff doesn't matter this is
the future of the PR man you gotta be
real it's everyday bro buy a fighter
yeah um you gotta fight gotta stand up
for what you believe in
my biggest accomplishment so far I
haven't done shit man
next play with the points who the points
points are gonna be good
next plan features um red light stop
signs 0.5 is gonna is gonna hopefully
change the game rather stop signs come
out in middle of the 0.4 series you are
gonna need a gray panda self-promoting
on periscope this is what I'm doing with
my Sunday school be Sunday this isn't
self promoting calm about a nice little
shop comedy I go buy our stuff right now
I wish that like Luca Paul is making a
killing off merch but you gotta you
gotta wonder how I mean he does have a
much bigger audience maybe that's how
he's doing it but like it's like if this
wasn't fun for me I wouldn't do it right
I do it because it's fun I do it cuz
like what else am i doing man this is
what I'm doing
make sure there's any more how's life
life is life is good um favorite other
AI company anyone is open sourcing stuff
man gotta open source your paper as open
source your code I do want some Tesla
stock I do own some Tesla stock I don't
some video stock i shorted mobile I lost
money on that shirt I bought some Fitbit
stock off that bad
and uh gone well nah man commas life
that's it do I like open source yeah
because I'll tell you why I like open
source because old-school hacker value
right no X market was a terrible movie
um because no problem should have to be
soft twice right like there's just this
is no point where one world man but one
world I think we can I think we can we
can move past it and come up with better
business models that don't involve like
like intellectual property is is
literally I talked about this in a
recent interview like you're really
ready to put a gun to someone's head cuz
they took your idea I mean not so you
have to be ready to do if you believe in
intellectual property if I wasn't doing
this what would I be doing oh no man
trying to build an AI girlfriend now
could I'd be building AI girlfriends for
the masses right seriously there's a
there's a big untapped market there I
mean imagine like you know shiver fur
for sex yeah
do I like black mirror yeah as a great
show that's a great show I don't know
this season I'm gonna say I wasn't a fan
of this season but like guys my face is
real washed out do I like Trump hair I
do for work in San Francisco I don't get
a salary you guys I don't spend money I
hobble crypto and I make money that's it
you got to keep it real bro there's a
lot of fake stuff in the world today and
that's why you got to keep it real like
fire festival kind of fake my iPhone
jailbroken no why would I jump right my
father who cares once I win then what
there's always more winning to be had
there is always more winning when you
think you've won never rest on your
laurels always just win harder think
about how to win do I listen to local
radio know what I think that you want to
take on AI think AI scares Elon for a
few reasons
I don't know I mean you think about like
someone was a very modernist view and
yai might scare them I mean that's said
that's kind of what I see and what I see
in Elon
I'm surprised that he talks about
getting government's involved that's
horrifying bro and think about any
weapons control treaty ever in history
you guys think of AI just like any other
weapon right it's a nuclear technology
right nuclear technology is incredible
it could be used for great things a bad
things um
Tesla vision chip I don't know why you
don't need to do that it's fine I would
sure like you biggie biggie like BAM
because honestly bro when you watch that
rocket launch you just feel so hyped for
the future you feel like that future
that we dreamed about is kids reading
sci-fi books is real right and that's I
mean that's all I want
all the winners of the great end of
February end of February biggest to
young users for the year and a failure
we'll try to do it do I know people that
went to fire festival bro I wish I went
to fire festival well I launched a song
very good space huge I mean that's
that's a very like modernist view right
like I can I can like it and I can
appreciate it it's not I mean my view is
very much more hey I want to move to
virtual I would if he one wants to die
on Mars I want to live forever in
virtual reality difference between
computer and Tesla three neon that Tesla
three has a much bigger computer I'm not
sure how much that matters Khamenei I
have racket we give racket do we play
tennis woo you know that song tennis
court by Lourdes and I saw but yeah so
I'm back at the house the main things
that I want to talk about airplanes
don't drive brother fly um
the main things that I want to talk
about the three things are the comma a I
retail shop probably not happening but
wouldn't that be cool but the things
that definitely definitely are happening
are number one we are hiring
four people four people we're looking
for people with react infrastructure
honestly reactive infrastructure could
easily fill four roles people who could
test people who can do a really good job
on making our products we got to get to
a five star experience you know because
that's what we got to be on on Amazon we
want all our products to be rated five
star and then some of them are if I
start quite yeah quite yeah you guys are
early adopters you'll know it the other
thing that I want to talk to you about
is we are gonna start shipping
we are gonna start shipping selenium you
mean the element that they killed the
bad guys with at the end of evolution
choose to move in LA no no a reselling
Pro is absolutely not bro
Tom I Oh s hardware support No why would
I do that
as I'm past hacking it was a cool way to
learn get over at jailbreaking is over
that error is over jailbreaking phones
is over phones are incredible you can
buy some great phones that are as
customizable as you want or if you want
the full Apple experience you you
understand like the reason you had to
jailbreak the first iPhone was because
you didn't have a choice
now if you want something to be open go
buy an essential phone right it's a
great phone um or go buy I mean there's
a bunch of open androids you know I'm a
big fan of one-plus I mean that's what
you do just just just just just spend
the money right um there's no point in
trying to like like to have our iPhone
anymore that era is over but the era
that's not over is jailbreaking cars
because you can't buy a half-decent car
except like Tesla's are pretty good but
you know they're very closed right
there's no there's no like Android
alternative to Tesla okay and they're
electric which like in theory I'm a fan
of electric cars but like if you like
live in an apartment proud were you
charging your electric car um I'm
actually my backyard right now and
consoles yeah it's all like a consoled
jailbreaking was always like bro PC
games PC master-race what's that on
reddit Google go to wine Google's gone
to shit how about that uh hey Google
Google Google has gone sharply downhill
in the last couple years it said it said
no I wouldn't I went is the beginning of
it in 2014
sad no I think that was his point
control custom rate like the thing about
piracy is it's just boring but stop
being poor just buy the shit
infrastructure people want to think
people who want to thank the people who
want to change the world because that's
what we're doing here comma or I mean
we're taking over I've never heard of
mythic AI but yeah so
recruiting and and shipping if you buy
stuff now it's gonna ship soon no more
no more long ship lags we're done with
that am I worried about way mo creating
massive rideshare Network yeah just like
I was worried about Google glass and
Google Fiber yeah alright alright
you're my rap fan I like I like my raps
to not that much it's okay my raps are
okay I could be a no I don't put enough
effort into the raps bro I wish I put
effort into some striving cars
bro Apple couldn't keep me out and Sony
couldn't keep me out you think Toyota's
gonna keep me out good luck for us
uber glass ya know I / fiber that's real
right
imagine uber took over the ISPs Comcast
to be crying to every on a jetpack uber
made over fiber I can't tolerate it now
but Hooper's / ubers / Travis if you're
out there and you're listening bro it's
turn on his pee pee let um what do I
think of uber I'm a huge uber fan um
just just just just the way Ober has
made my life better in the last five
years it's great I love you goobers
everywhere um so I'm a huge again I'm
not talking about the company but I'm
talking about like the idea and the
execution right